Guide to the Annual Reports 1973-2009 [Call #]
Eastern Connecticut State University, Publisher
- Series III - 1990-1994
  - Academic Affairs: Psychology (2), 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Academic Affairs: Psychology (3), 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Academic Affairs: Sociology, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Academic Affairs: Sociology (2), 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Academic Affairs: Honors Program, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Academic Affairs: Writing Program, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Continuing Education, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Professional Education, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Professional Education (2), 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Academic Affairs: Business Administration, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Academic Affairs: Business Administration (2), 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Academic Affairs: Communication, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Academic Affairs: Communication (2), 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Academic Affairs: Economics, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Academic Affairs: Economics (2), 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - Academic Affairs: Education, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Academic Affairs: Education (2), 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Academic Affairs: Health and Physical Education, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Administrative: Affirmative Action Office, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - Administrative: Athletics, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - Administrative: Athletics (2), 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - Administrative: Institutional Advancement, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Administrative: Financial Aid, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - Administrative: Health Services, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Administrative: Health Services (2), 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - Administrative: Housing and Residential Life, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - Administrative: Housing and Residential Life (2), 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - Administrative: International Program, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Administrative: New Student Orientation, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Administrative: Office of Finance and Administration, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Administrative: Office of Finance and Administration (2), 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Administrative: Office of Finance and Administration (3), 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Administrative: Personnel Administration, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Administrative: Planning and Institutional Research, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Administrative: Public Safety, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Administrative: Public Safety (2), 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Administrative: Student Affairs, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Administrative: Student Center/Activities, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Series IV - 1995-1999
  - Academic Affairs: Executive Summary, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Academic Affairs: Academic Grants Officer, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Academic Affairs: Admissions and Enrollment, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Academic Affairs: Akus Gallery, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Academic Affairs: Center for Education Excellence, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Academic Affairs: David Chase Institute, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Academic Affairs: International Studies, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Academic Affairs: Learning Center, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Academic Affairs: Library, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Academic Affairs: Library (2), 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Academic Affairs: Library (3), 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Academic Affairs: Library (4), 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Academic Affairs: Library (5), 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Academic Affairs: Library (6), 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Academic Affairs: Library (7), 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Academic Affairs: Library (8), 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Academic Affairs: Media Center, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Academic Affairs: Registrars Office, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Arts and Science, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Arts and Science (2), 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Arts and Science (3), 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Academic Affairs: Biology, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Academic Affairs: English, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Academic Affairs: English (2), 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Academic Affairs: English (3), 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Academic Affairs: English (4), 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Academic Affairs: Environmental Earth Science, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Academic Affairs: Fine Arts, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Academic Affairs: Fine Arts (2), 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Academic Affairs: Fine Arts (3), 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Academic Affairs: Fine Arts (4), 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Academic Affairs: History/Philosophy/Political Science, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Academic Affairs:, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Academic Affairs:, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Academic Affairs:, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Academic Affairs: Mathematics and Computer Science, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Academic Affairs: Modern and Classical Languages, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Academic Affairs: Physical Science, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Academic Affairs: Psychology, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Academic Affairs: Psychology (2), 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Academic Affairs: Psychology (3), 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Academic Affairs: Sociology, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Academic Affairs: Sociology (2), 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Academic Affairs: Sociology (3), 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Academic Affairs: Sociology (4), 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Academic Affairs: American Studies Program, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Academic Affairs: Canadian Studies, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Academic Affairs: Latin American Studies, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Academic Affairs: University Honors, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Academic Affairs: Women's Studies, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Academic Affairs: Writing Program, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Continuing Education, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Professional Studies, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Professional Studies (2), 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Professional Studies (3), 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Academic Affairs: Business Administration, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Academic Affairs: Business Administration (2), 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Academic Affairs: Business Administration (3), 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Academic Affairs: Communication, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Academic Affairs: Communication (2), 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Academic Affairs: Economics, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Academic Affairs: Economics (2), 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Academic Affairs: Education, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Academic Affairs: Education (2), 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Academic Affairs: Health and Physical Education, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - University Relations, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Academic Affairs: Vice President's Executive Summary, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Academic Affairs: Vice President's Executive Summary, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Academic Affairs: Academic Grant Officer, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Academic Affairs: Advisement Center, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Academic Affairs: Akus Gallery, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Academic Affairs: Akus Gallery (2), 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Academic Affairs: Center for Educational Excellence, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Academic Affairs: David Chase Institute, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Academic Affairs: International Studies, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Academic Affairs: Learning Center, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - Academic Affairs: Library, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Academic Affairs: Library (2), 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Academic Affairs: Library (3), 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - Academic Affairs: Library (4), 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - Academic Affairs: Library (5), 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - Academic Affairs: Library (6), 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - Academic Affairs: Media Services, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - Academic Affairs: Registrar, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Arts and Science, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Arts and Science (2), 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 96)
  - Academic Affairs: Biology, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 97)
  - Academic Affairs: English, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 98)
  - Academic Affairs: English (2), 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 99)
  - Academic Affairs: English (3), 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 100)
  - Academic Affairs: Environmental Earth Science, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 101)
  - Academic Affairs: Fine Arts, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 102)
  - Academic Affairs: Fine Arts (2), 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 103)
  - Academic Affairs: Fine Arts (3), 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 104)
  - Academic Affairs: Fine Arts (4), 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 105)
  - Academic Affairs: Fine Arts (5), 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 106)
  - Academic Affairs: History/Political Science/Philosophy, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Academic Affairs:, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Academic Affairs: Mathematics/Computer Science, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Academic Affairs: Mathematics/Computer Science (2), 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Academic Affairs: Modern & Classical Language, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Academic Affairs: Modern & Classical Language (2), 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Academic Affairs: Physical Science, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Academic Affairs: Psychology, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Academic Affairs: Sociology, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Academic Affairs: Sociology (2), 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Academic Affairs: Sociology (3), 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Academic Affairs: Writing Program, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Academic Affairs: Women's Studies, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Continuing Education, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Professional Studies (2), 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Professional Studies (3), 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Academic Affairs: Business Administration, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Academic Affairs: Business Administration (2), 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Academic Affairs: Business Administration (3), 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Academic Affairs: Communications, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Academic Affairs: Communications (2), 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Academic Affairs: Communications (3), 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Academic Affairs: Economics, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Academic Affairs: Economics (2), 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Academic Affairs: Education, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Academic Affairs: Education (2), 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Academic Affairs: Education (3), 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Academic Affairs: Education (4), 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Academic Affairs: Education (5), 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Academic Affairs: Health and Physical Education, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Academic Affairs: Health and Physical Education (2), 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Professional Studies, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Affirmative Action, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Athletics, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Athletics (2), 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Auxiliary Enterprises, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Campus Student Judicial, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Career and Experiential Education, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Counseling Services, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Data Center, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Facilities, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Facilities (2), 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Finance and Administrative, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Financial Aid, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Health Services, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Housing and Residential Life, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Housing and Residential Life (2), 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Institutional Advancement, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Institutional Advancement (2), 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - National Student Exchange (N.S.E) Program, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Orientation Program, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Personnel Administration, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Planning and Institutional Research, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Public Relations, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Public Safety, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Public Safety (2), 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Student Center, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Student Development, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - University Relations, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - University Relations (2), 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - University Relations (3), 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - University Relations (4), 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - University Relations (5), 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - University Relations (6), 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - University Relations (7), 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - University Relations (8), 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - University Relations (9), 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Academic Affairs: Vice President's Executive Summary, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Academic Affairs: Academic Grant Officer, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Academic Affairs: Admissions and Enrollment Planning, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - Academic Affairs:, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Academic Affairs: Advisement Center, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - Academic Affairs: Akus Gallery, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - Academic Affairs: Center for Educational Excellence, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - Academic Affairs: Learning Center, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - Academic Affairs: Library, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - Academic Affairs: Library (2), 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 77)
  - Academic Affairs: Library (3), 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - Academic Affairs: Library (4), 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - Academic Affairs: Library (5), 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - Academic Affairs: Registrar Office, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 81)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Arts and Science, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 82)
  - Academic Affairs: Biology, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 83)
  - Academic Affairs: Biology (2), 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 84)
  - Academic Affairs: English, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 85)
  - Academic Affairs: English (2), 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 86)
  - Academic Affairs: English (3), 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 87)
  - Academic Affairs: Environmental Earth Science, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 88)
  - Academic Affairs: Fine Arts, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Academic Affairs: Fine Arts (2), 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Academic Affairs: Fine Arts (3), 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Academic Affairs: History/Philosophy/Political Science, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Academic Affairs:, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Academic Affairs:, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Academic Affairs:, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Academic Affairs:, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Academic Affairs:, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Academic Affairs:, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Academic Affairs: Modern and Classical Languages (2), 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Academic Affairs: Physical Science, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Academic Affairs: Psychology, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Academic Affairs: Psychology (2), 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Academic Affairs: Sociology, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Academic Affairs: Sociology (2), 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Academic Affairs: Sociology (3), 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Continuing Education, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Professional Studies, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Professional Studies (2), 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Professional Studies (3), 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Academic Affairs: Business Administration, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Academic Affairs: Business Administration (2), 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Academic Affairs: Business Administration (3), 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Academic Affairs: Communication, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Academic Affairs: Communication (2), 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Academic Affairs: Communication (3), 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Academic Affairs: Economics, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Academic Affairs: Economics (2), 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Academic Affairs: Education, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Academic Affairs: Education (2), 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Academic Affairs: Education (3), 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Academic Affairs: Education (4), 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Academic Affairs: Education (5), 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Academic Affairs: Education (6), 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Academic Affairs: Education (7), 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Academic Affairs: Health and Physical Education, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Academic Affairs: Health and Physical Education (2), 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Affirmative Action Office, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Alumni and Development, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Athletics, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Athletics (2), 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Auxiliary Enterprises, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Campus Judicial System, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Career and Experimental Education, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Counseling Services, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Data Center, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Data Center (2), 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Facilities Management and Planning, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Facilities Management and Planning (2), 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Financial and Administrative, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Financial Aid, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Fiscal Affairs, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Health Services, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Institutional Advancement, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - International Program, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Personnel Office, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Personnel Office (2), 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Planning and Institutional Research, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Planning and Institutional Research (2), 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Public Safety, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Public Safety (2), 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Student Affairs, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Student Affairs (2), 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Student Affairs (3), 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Student Affairs (4), 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Student Affairs (5), 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Student Center/Activities, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Substance Abuse Prevention, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - University Relation, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - University Relation (2), 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - University Relation (3), 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - Academic Affairs: Vice President's Executive Summary, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - Academic Affairs: Academic Grant's Office, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - Academic Affairs: Admissions and Enrollment Planning, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - Academic Affairs: Admissions and Enrollment Planning, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - Academic Affairs: Advisement Center, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - Academic Affairs: Advisement Center (2), 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - Academic Affairs: Akus Gallery, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - Academic Affairs: Center for Educational Excellence, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - Academic Affairs: David Chase Institute, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - Academic Affairs: Learning Center, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - Academic Affairs: Library, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - Academic Affairs: Library (2), 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - Academic Affairs: Library (3), 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - Academic Affairs: Library (4), 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - Academic Affairs: Library (5), 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 87)
  - Academic Affairs: Library (6), 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - Academic Affairs: Media Services, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 89)
  - Academic Affairs: Registrar's Office, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 90)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Arts and Science, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 91)
  - Academic Affairs: Biology, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 92)
  - Academic Affairs: Biology (2), 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 93)
  - Academic Affairs: English, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 94)
  - Academic Affairs: English (2), 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 95)
  - Academic Affairs: English (3), 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 96)
  - Academic Affairs: English (4), 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 97)
  - Academic Affairs: English (5), 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 98)
  - Academic Affairs: English (6), 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 99)
  - Academic Affairs: English (7), 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 100)
  - Academic Affairs: Environmental Earth Science, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 101)
  - Academic Affairs: Fine Arts (1), 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Academic Affairs: Fine Arts (2), 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Academic Affairs: Fine Arts (3), 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Academic Affairs: Fine Arts (4), 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Academic Affairs: Fine Arts (5), 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Academic Affairs: Fine Arts (6), 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Academic Affairs: History/Philosophy/Political Science, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Academic Affairs:, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Academic Affairs:, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Academic Affairs:, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Academic Affairs:, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Academic Affairs: Mathematics and Computer Science, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Academic Affairs:, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Academic Affairs:, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Academic Affairs: Modern and Classical Languages, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Academic Affairs: Modern and Classical Languages (2), 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Academic Affairs: Physical Science, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Academic Affairs: Psychology, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Academic Affairs: Psychology (2), 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Academic Affairs: Sociology, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Academic Affairs: Sociology (2), 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Academic Affairs: Sociology (3), 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Academic Affairs: Sociology (4), 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Academic Affairs: Sociology (5), 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Continuing Education, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Professional Studies, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Professional Studies (2), 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Academic Affairs: Business Administration, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Academic Affairs: Business Administration (2), 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Academic Affairs: Business Administration (3), 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 30)